<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Useful Terror</name>
	<author>Fuu Chan</author>
	<packageId>Fuu.UsefulTerror</packageId>
	<description>
Building a horror base filled with skullspikes and gibbets was one of the more interesting possibilities in Ideology, but it turned out terror was never needed and redundant with the collar and body strap. In addition, the way terror worked was janky at best, slow to apply because the observation check has a low tick rate, yet quick to fade when the 5 cell observation range gets surpassed. So I changed it!

Primary Changes:
Configurable multiplier for Time Until Rebellion and Time Until Prison Break
1. In Mod Options, sliders from 10% (10 times as often) to 1000% (10 times less often)

Give terror a non-redundant benefit, and make it less janky:
1. Terror can be used to weaken or nullify the "weapon proximity", "escape route", and "unattended" rebellion penalties. Meaning that outdoor work, hauling/smelting in the armory, assisting in fighting, or even leaving the map with all your colonists is now possible as long as there is sufficient terror coverage.
2. The terror object observation will remain for 4 in-game hours instead of immediately ending once out of the 5 cell range of the terror object.

Smarter suppression logic:
1. Wardens will suppress when suppression is under 90%, up from 70%.
2. If suppression loss per day is 0%, wardens will suppress if suppression is under 100%.

New heart acidifier implant:
1. A mini-acidifier installed next to the heart to instill permanent terror in slaves. Causes a slave to have 100% terror anywhere in the world regardless of terror objects. Unlocked by the Poison Synthesis research.

Modified Bliss Lobotomy:
1. Adds a 100% terror effect to Bliss Lobotomy surgery from Anomaly, which serves as an earlier game alternative to the heart acidifier with more severe downsides.

Terror values adjusted, because there was no reason to use Gibbets or Terror sculptures over the cheaper and better Skullspikes.
1. Gibbet buffed to 50 terror, up from 25 terror.
2. Terror sculpture buffed to 40 terror, up from 10 terror, +-5 per quality difference.
3. Skullspikes are now lightweight objects like Torches, so they can be placed in sand/swampy terrain, over stockpile zones, won't block wind turbines, and be easily walked over.
4. Placing/selecting terror structures will now show the terror radius.

The combined effect is that terror will both serve a unique role and be an important consideration in base design.

Compatibility
*0% performance impact (Less than 0.001ms average in Dub's Performance Analyzer).

*Safe to add and remove mid-game (remove the heart acidifier from anyone with it first).		

*Independent, isolated, and minimal in scope, with no unsafe modifications to vanilla behavior/code: Should be compatible with nearly every mod, leaves no permanent changes to your saved game, and will not brick your game.

*Confirmed compatible with Combat Extended, Vanilla Expanded series, Alpha series, Dubs series, and hundreds more.

Updates
~3.2 update: Add 100% terror effect to Bliss Lobotomy surgery from Anomaly, which serves as an earlier game alternative to the heart acidifier with more severe downsides.
~3.1 update: New Time until Prison Break and Time until Slave Rebellion multiplier added in the options! The time until the next prison break and rebellion can now be decreased or increased to fit your preference!
~3.0 update: Now compatible with 1.5! Heart acidifier should no longer spawn on enemies.
~2.2 update: Heart Acidifer will now require the Poison Synthesis research instead of Bionics if Royalty is installed.
~2.1 update: Fixed Heart Acidifier to not be dependent on owning Royalty.
~2.0 update:
- Now compatible with 1.4!
- New Heart Acidifier implant!
- Terror observation effect will now remain for 4 in-game hours, up from 1 hour. This should feel better gameplay wise and will allow for nicer base design, rather than requiring terror coverage for every inch of the base.
- Smart logic to ensure wardens maintain 100% suppression if suppression loss per day is 0%.
- Removed the nerfs to Body straps and Collar, because it was over-complexity and bloat for no real gameplay improvement.
~1.02 update: Removed the meditation focus radius indicator from terror sculptures because double radius indicators is too confusing.
~1.01 update: Added terror radius indicator when placing/selecting terror structures.

Github Link: https://github.com/tenguin/Rimworld_UsefulTerror

Credits to: grape05843924, corviwing, Mint Fantome, and Pomu Rainpuff for the art sources used in the thumbnail and tanosii_chan for the upvote animation! Give them a visit!
	</description>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.3</li>
		<li>1.4</li>
		<li>1.5</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>ludeon.rimworld.ideology</packageId>
			<displayName>Ideology</displayName>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Anomaly</li>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
	</loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>